scoopnyc.com 2016-06-26

# Scoop NYC | Privacy Policy - Responsive

#### PRIVACY POLICY Last updated June 1, 2010

Scoopnyc.com is owned by Scoop Web LLC. Scoopnyc.com is committed to providing our customers with the highest quality products and services. We use the information we gather from our interactions with you to improve your shopping experience. Because we respect your privacy, we have instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner. Please review this Privacy Statement periodically for up-to-date information as this policy may change with the latest technology.

#### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you shop with Scoopnyc.com, we obtain information from you in order to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card number.

When you register with us as an online customer or participate in one of our online promotions, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, gender, interests, product preferences or favorite designers.

To improve our web site, we may collect non-personal information about how users navigate through the site. We use "cookies" and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information. Cookies are small pieces of information sent from a Web server to your computer. These allow us to personalize, customize and quickly process and complete your shopping experience without having to continually request the same basic information from you. Cookies are not used to store any personal information such as name, address or payment information.

#### USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We use the information we collect to process your purchase transactions, to keep you informed about the status of your orders, to send you marketing and promotional materials by mail or e-mail and to improve our product assortments, customer service and overall shopping experience.

We may provide information we collect to carefully selected third-party service providers that help us bring you our products and services. For example, we may work with an outside company to assist us in distributing emails.

#### SECURITY

The security of your information is very important to us. We work to protect the security of your information during order transmission by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the order information you transmit. Once you enter the checkout page, your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. You can tell that you are in secure mode when the "http" in the web address is replaced by "https." Scoopnyc.com strives to protect your information and privacy on our Website, however no data transmission over the internet is 100% secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online. You also play a role in protecting your information. If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to log out at the conclusion of your session. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.
